<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<nicovideo_thumb_response status="ok"><thumb><video_id>sm44815305</video_id><title>Resume Well podcast created by Courtney Page. with Richard Blank</title><description>Re:sume Well is your essential guide to thriving in both your career and personal life, featuring deep-dive conversations with industry leaders who share battle-tested strategies for sustainable success. Each episode delivers actionable insights on everything from mindful productivity and stress management to work-life integration and corporate wellness initiatives, helping you build a career and life that energizes rather than depletes. Whether you're a seasoned executive, entrepreneur, or early in your professional journey, join us to discover how to work well, live well, and Re:sume Well.In this episode, Richard and I are chatting about his love for the Spanish language growing up, how that led him down to Costa Rica, and how that eventually sparked his CEO journey owning a call center. Richard is such a kind, open soul, so it’s no wonder he brings that light to his employees and everyone around him. It’s a refreshing departure from what we normally expect out of call center experiences, and for that, we can https://youtu.be/Ww4MUb3vkO4https://youtu.be/U_2DFeR1b1whttps://youtu.be/fVXrAeADvDUhttps://youtu.be/Vq5-eu5UPLs</description><thumbnail_url>https://nicovideo.cdn.nimg.jp/thumbnails/44815305/44815305.60297822</thumbnail_url><first_retrieve>2025-03-29T03:19:03+09:00</first_retrieve><length>46:32</length><movie_type>mp4</movie_type><size_high>1</size_high><size_low>1</size_low><view_counter>7</view_counter><comment_num>0</comment_num><mylist_counter>0</mylist_counter><last_res_body/><watch_url>https://www.nicovideo.jp/watch/sm44815305</watch_url><thumb_type>video</thumb_type><embeddable>1</embeddable><no_live_play>0</no_live_play><tags domain="jp"/><genre>未設定</genre><user_id>129827043</user_id><user_nickname>richardblank444</user_nickname><user_icon_url>https://secure-dcdn.cdn.nimg.jp/nicoaccount/usericon/12982/129827043.jpg?1709157045</user_icon_url></thumb></nicovideo_thumb_response>
