<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<nicovideo_thumb_response status="ok"><thumb><video_id>sm45002118</video_id><title>The B2B Influence Podcast. The Importance of Relationship-Building in Telesales with Richard Blank</title><description>Are you a leader making waves in the B2B marketing space? The B2B Influence podcast is an exclusive The B2B Influence Podcast by The Marketing Vanguard.  Episode 10 - Building Bridges, Not Barriers: The Importance of Relationship-Building in Telemarketing with Costa Rica's Call CenterIn this episode of The Marketing Vanguard: Leading Voices in B2B Innovation, Paula Chiocchi interviews the President, CEO, and Bilingual Telemarketing Trainer of Costa Rica's Call Center, Richard Blank. Richard explores the crucial role of call centers in the marketing-to-sales pipeline, emphasizing the importance of human connection and empathy in telemarketing.Richard discusses balancing inbound and outbound calls, the significance of soft skills, and the operational challenges of converting leads. He advocates for quality interactions over quantity, effective follow-up, and maintaining realistic expectations. Richard underscores the enduring value of personal connections in customer service and telemarketing.https://youtu.be/bzJze5vXiuMhttps://youtu.be/yIF8TGySqIAhttps://youtu.be/w8aGC09Yy-4https://youtu.be/MZT8pkqrdDohttps://youtu.be/bfJrFeS06FM</description><thumbnail_url>https://nicovideo.cdn.nimg.jp/thumbnails/45002118/45002118.44841476</thumbnail_url><first_retrieve>2025-05-20T02:22:03+09:00</first_retrieve><length>24:18</length><movie_type>mp4</movie_type><size_high>1</size_high><size_low>1</size_low><view_counter>0</view_counter><comment_num>0</comment_num><mylist_counter>0</mylist_counter><last_res_body/><watch_url>https://www.nicovideo.jp/watch/sm45002118</watch_url><thumb_type>video</thumb_type><embeddable>1</embeddable><no_live_play>0</no_live_play><tags domain="jp"/><genre>未設定</genre><user_id>129827043</user_id><user_nickname>richardblank444</user_nickname><user_icon_url>https://secure-dcdn.cdn.nimg.jp/nicoaccount/usericon/12982/129827043.jpg?1709157045</user_icon_url></thumb></nicovideo_thumb_response>
