<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<nicovideo_thumb_response status="ok"><thumb><video_id>sm45070475</video_id><title>The First 15 Minutes of Castlevania Chronicle: 悪魔城ドラキュラ (PlayStation)</title><description>Copied from PlayStation DataCenter:Whenever Dracula rises from the dead, a Belmont is there, ready to invade the ever-changing castle and send Dracula back to the hell that spawned him. In this Castlevania adventure, the man who started it all once again returns to the stage. Simon Belmont will have to whip his way through the dark halls of the Lord Vampire's castle, taking down his minions and eventually doing battle with Dracula himself.Castlevania Chronicles is the first opportunity a majority of U.S. gamers have to play one of the few Castlevania games that was never released stateside. Originally titled Dracula X68000, the game was released in Japan on the Sharp X68000 in 1993 and harkens back to the original days of the series on the NES and MSX computer.In addition to the Original mode, which is a port of the Sharp X68000 game, Chronicles adds an Arranged mode. This version of the game offers some updated music and new graphics handled by Ayami Kojima.</description><thumbnail_url>https://nicovideo.cdn.nimg.jp/thumbnails/45070475/45070475.48952748</thumbnail_url><first_retrieve>2025-06-09T12:19:03+09:00</first_retrieve><length>15:00</length><movie_type>mp4</movie_type><size_high>1</size_high><size_low>1</size_low><view_counter>1</view_counter><comment_num>0</comment_num><mylist_counter>0</mylist_counter><last_res_body/><watch_url>https://www.nicovideo.jp/watch/sm45070475</watch_url><thumb_type>video</thumb_type><embeddable>1</embeddable><no_live_play>0</no_live_play><tags domain="jp"><tag lock="1">CastlevaniaChronicles</tag><tag lock="1">悪魔城年代記</tag><tag lock="1">PlayStation</tag><tag lock="1">PS1</tag><tag lock="1">プレイステーション</tag><tag lock="1">gameplay</tag></tags><genre>ゲーム</genre><user_id>123226612</user_id><user_nickname>The_VNS</user_nickname><user_icon_url>https://secure-dcdn.cdn.nimg.jp/nicoaccount/usericon/12322/123226612.jpg?1646346916</user_icon_url></thumb></nicovideo_thumb_response>
