<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<nicovideo_thumb_response status="ok"><thumb><video_id>sm44852802</video_id><title>The First 15 Minutes of Tomb Raider: The Last Revelation (Dreamcast)</title><description>Copied from MobyGames:According to Egyptian legend, Horus outwitted the evil god Set and imprisoned him in a secret tomb...Five thousand years later, Lara Croft discovers the lost tomb and unwittingly unleashes the Set, fulfilling the ancient prophecy of his return to plunge mankind into darkness! In a race against time, Lara must use all of her wit and skill to re-imprison Set and save the world from Armageddon.Tomb Raider: The Last Revelation plays very similar to the previous games in the series, but some new things have been added to the game. The biggest addition is that now rather large parts of the game consist of several interconnected levels sometimes explored in any order, with puzzles in one level often requiring that some actions are done in other levels. Lara has also learned a few new moves: she can climb into the niches with low ceilings, she can now move around the corners while hanging and she can also pull levers and open trap-doors while jumping.</description><thumbnail_url>https://nicovideo.cdn.nimg.jp/thumbnails/44852802/44852802.99183984</thumbnail_url><first_retrieve>2025-04-07T22:39:03+09:00</first_retrieve><length>15:00</length><movie_type>mp4</movie_type><size_high>1</size_high><size_low>1</size_low><view_counter>5</view_counter><comment_num>0</comment_num><mylist_counter>0</mylist_counter><last_res_body/><watch_url>https://www.nicovideo.jp/watch/sm44852802</watch_url><thumb_type>video</thumb_type><embeddable>1</embeddable><no_live_play>0</no_live_play><tags domain="jp"><tag lock="1">TombRaider_TheLastRevelation</tag><tag lock="1">トゥームレイダー4</tag><tag lock="1">Dreamcast</tag><tag lock="1">DC</tag><tag lock="1">ドリームキャスト</tag><tag lock="1">gameplay</tag></tags><genre>ゲーム</genre><user_id>123226612</user_id><user_nickname>The_VNS</user_nickname><user_icon_url>https://secure-dcdn.cdn.nimg.jp/nicoaccount/usericon/12322/123226612.jpg?1646346916</user_icon_url></thumb></nicovideo_thumb_response>
