<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<nicovideo_thumb_response status="ok"><thumb><video_id>sm44838376</video_id><title>Aliens: Fireteam Elite - Promise of a Flower: Strike | AVPUNKNOWN</title><description>As we descend further into the hive’s abyss, we uncover its dark, pulsating core the very heart of this nightmare. And there, lurking in the shadows, we find her… the Queen of the Pathogens. A being of pure terror, a monstrosity beyond comprehension the ultimate apex predator. She is not just a leader; she is an unstoppable force of nature, the architect of annihilation. If we fail, her spawn will spread like wildfire, consuming everything in their path until nothing remains but death and decay.But we are Marines. We don’t back down. We don’t break. We fight. And tonight, we make our stand. Lock and load, because if we don’t stop her now, there won’t be a second chance.Let’s send this monster back to hell! Big thx/shoutout to my pal  @b1kingkenny  for providing great technical and fire support! go check his channel out for Aliens | Predator | AVP Game Content! Alright sweethearts, you heard the man! And you know the drill, assholes and elbows! Buy Aliens: Fireteam Elite (STEAM/PC) https://store.steampowered.com/app/1549970/Aliens_Fireteam_Elite/</description><thumbnail_url>https://nicovideo.cdn.nimg.jp/thumbnails/44838376/44838376.26802331</thumbnail_url><first_retrieve>2025-04-03T07:56:04+09:00</first_retrieve><length>23:48</length><movie_type>mp4</movie_type><size_high>1</size_high><size_low>1</size_low><view_counter>8</view_counter><comment_num>0</comment_num><mylist_counter>0</mylist_counter><last_res_body/><watch_url>https://www.nicovideo.jp/watch/sm44838376</watch_url><thumb_type>video</thumb_type><embeddable>1</embeddable><no_live_play>0</no_live_play><tags domain="jp"/><genre>ゲーム</genre><user_id>116672729</user_id><user_nickname>AVPUNKNOWN</user_nickname><user_icon_url>https://secure-dcdn.cdn.nimg.jp/nicoaccount/usericon/11667/116672729.jpg?1606699817</user_icon_url></thumb></nicovideo_thumb_response>
