<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<nicovideo_thumb_response status="ok"><thumb><video_id>sm45174654</video_id><title>Off the comma podcast guest Richard Blank Costa Ricas Call Center</title><description>Episode 79 of Off the Comma podcast lands today and I’m talking with Richard Blank from Costa Rica. In this episode, we talk to Richard Blank. He is empathetic, confident and has “old school grit”. Richard lives in Costa Rica. Richard tells us about getting off the comma created by familial and societal expectations. Growing up in a world where he was expected to follow a prescribed path, Richard describes feeling like he didn’t fit in and appearing as a failure to those around him. Allowing himself to “fail out” led him to find a new path and surprise himself with what he would find along the way. Paying attention to his instincts and the signs along the way, he ultimately found himself in another country, speaking a different language, and enjoying a success he never imagined. Tune in to hear what Richard means when he says “friends tell me they wish they had tried”. https://youtu.be/UjjNcZ79crMhttps://youtu.be/clTjtxUt8UQ?si=XsocL8_ZbFZxE_9mRichard Blank hired bassist Garry Gary Beers of INXS. https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ieGjN5H4xPQ</description><thumbnail_url>https://nicovideo.cdn.nimg.jp/thumbnails/45174654/45174654.81868293</thumbnail_url><first_retrieve>2025-07-11T03:51:03+09:00</first_retrieve><length>63:41</length><movie_type>mp4</movie_type><size_high>1</size_high><size_low>1</size_low><view_counter>0</view_counter><comment_num>0</comment_num><mylist_counter>0</mylist_counter><last_res_body/><watch_url>https://www.nicovideo.jp/watch/sm45174654</watch_url><thumb_type>video</thumb_type><embeddable>1</embeddable><no_live_play>0</no_live_play><tags domain="jp"/><genre>未設定</genre><user_id>140805938</user_id><user_nickname>richardblank</user_nickname><user_icon_url>https://secure-dcdn.cdn.nimg.jp/nicoaccount/usericon/defaults/blank.jpg</user_icon_url></thumb></nicovideo_thumb_response>
