<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<nicovideo_thumb_response status="ok"><thumb><video_id>sm45097923</video_id><title>Deutschlandlied, Horst Wessel, Wenn Alle Untreu</title><description>【注意事項 / Disclaimer】このコンテンツは、歴史研究、教育、または批評的な分析を目的として公開されています。ここに収録されている楽曲は、ナチス・ドイツ時代に制作・使用されたプロパガンダの一部です。これらの楽曲を公開する目的は、当時のプロパガンダが社会に与えた影響を理解するための歴史的資料を提供することにあります。制作者は、ナチズム、国家社会主義、ファシズム、反ユダヤ主義、人種差別、その他あらゆる全体主義的思想や政治的信条を、断固として拒絶します。このコンテンツをもって、これらの思想を称賛、正当化、または宣伝する意図は全くありません。歴史の悲劇を忘れず、同様の過ちが繰り返されないことを願う立場から公開するものです。閲覧にはご注意ください。[Disclaimer] This content is published for the purpose of historical research, education, or critical analysis. The music contained herein is a part of the propaganda created and used during the Nazi Germany era. The purpose of this upload is to provide historical material for understanding the influence of propaganda on society at that time. The uploader firmly rejects Nazism, National Socialism, fascism, anti-Semitism, racism, and any other totalitarian ideologies or political beliefs. There is absolutely no intention to praise, justify, or promote these ideologies with this content. This is being shared from the standpoint of hoping that the tragedies of history are not forgotten and that similar mistakes are not repeated. Viewer discretion is advised.</description><thumbnail_url>https://nicovideo.cdn.nimg.jp/thumbnails/45097923/45097923.84994764</thumbnail_url><first_retrieve>2025-06-17T22:25:03+09:00</first_retrieve><length>3:53</length><movie_type>mp4</movie_type><size_high>1</size_high><size_low>1</size_low><view_counter>8</view_counter><comment_num>0</comment_num><mylist_counter>0</mylist_counter><last_res_body/><watch_url>https://www.nicovideo.jp/watch/sm45097923</watch_url><thumb_type>video</thumb_type><embeddable>1</embeddable><no_live_play>1</no_live_play><tags domain="jp"/><genre>未設定</genre><user_id>121275121</user_id><user_nickname>はむ</user_nickname><user_icon_url>https://secure-dcdn.cdn.nimg.jp/nicoaccount/usericon/12127/121275121.jpg?1713370151</user_icon_url></thumb></nicovideo_thumb_response>
