<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<nicovideo_thumb_response status="ok"><thumb><video_id>sm45221655</video_id><title>Vision, Technology, Innovation and Money podcast. Host Ronen Chen interview with CEO Richard Blank</title><description>Vision, Technology, Innovation and Money podcast. Host Ronen Chen interview with CEO Richard BlankIn this inspiring episode of On Vision, Technology, Innovation and Money, we sit down with Richard Blank, CEO of Costa Rica’s Call Center. Richard shares his bold journey from Philadelphia to Costa Rica, where he built a thriving business and a life aligned with his values. We dive into his cutting-edge telemarketing techniques, leadership philosophy, the psychology of sales, and even the legendary “Buffer-Boomerang” close. Plus, hear how a childhood dream led him to amass Costa Rica’s largest collection of restored American pinball machines and jukeboxes. A wild mix of vision, grit, and vintage rock’n’roll—don’t miss it!Join technological visionary Ronen Chen as he delves into the world of innovation, technology, and business through engaging conversations with industry experts. Leveraging his expertise in behavioral economics and software development, Ronen explores how these disciplines drive creativity and inspire groundbreaking product ideas within the companies he collaborates with.https://youtu.be/e9i1IZ8YBGA</description><thumbnail_url>https://nicovideo.cdn.nimg.jp/thumbnails/45221655/45221655.65241273</thumbnail_url><first_retrieve>2025-07-25T02:56:03+09:00</first_retrieve><length>29:12</length><movie_type>mp4</movie_type><size_high>1</size_high><size_low>1</size_low><view_counter>0</view_counter><comment_num>0</comment_num><mylist_counter>0</mylist_counter><last_res_body/><watch_url>https://www.nicovideo.jp/watch/sm45221655</watch_url><thumb_type>video</thumb_type><embeddable>1</embeddable><no_live_play>0</no_live_play><tags domain="jp"/><genre>未設定</genre><user_id>140805938</user_id><user_nickname>richardblank</user_nickname><user_icon_url>https://secure-dcdn.cdn.nimg.jp/nicoaccount/usericon/defaults/blank.jpg</user_icon_url></thumb></nicovideo_thumb_response>
