<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<nicovideo_thumb_response status="ok"><thumb><video_id>sm44875274</video_id><title>The First 15 Minutes of Amerzone: The Explorer's Legacy (PlayStation)</title><description>Copied from MobyGames:In 1932, Alexandre Valembois was a young explorer who wanted to make a name for himself by exploring the mysterious Amerzone region. Befriended by the natives of the region, he witnessed a strange ritual involving a giant egg of the famed white birds. Wanting to prove that the white birds existed, Alexandre stole the mysterious egg and betrayed the natives' trust. Sixty years have passed and the world has changed. The Amerzone remains unexplored and closed off to outsiders by it's despotic leader. Monsieur Alexandre Valembois is an old man at the end of his life. At this time, a young reporter comes to visit the old Alexandre Valembois regarding his adventures...Amerzone is a first person adventure game, taking place between different rooms and areas. The player assumes the role of the reporter and must unravel the clues left by Monsieur Valembois, travelling over several picturesque locations and eventually reaching the fictional Amerzone region.</description><thumbnail_url>https://nicovideo.cdn.nimg.jp/thumbnails/44875274/44875274.30527612</thumbnail_url><first_retrieve>2025-04-14T09:39:03+09:00</first_retrieve><length>15:00</length><movie_type>mp4</movie_type><size_high>1</size_high><size_low>1</size_low><view_counter>2</view_counter><comment_num>0</comment_num><mylist_counter>0</mylist_counter><last_res_body/><watch_url>https://www.nicovideo.jp/watch/sm44875274</watch_url><thumb_type>video</thumb_type><embeddable>1</embeddable><no_live_play>0</no_live_play><tags domain="jp"><tag lock="1">Amerzone</tag><tag lock="1">アメゾン</tag><tag lock="1">PlayStation</tag><tag lock="1">PS1</tag><tag lock="1">プレイステーション</tag><tag lock="1">gameplay</tag></tags><genre>ゲーム</genre><user_id>123226612</user_id><user_nickname>The_VNS</user_nickname><user_icon_url>https://secure-dcdn.cdn.nimg.jp/nicoaccount/usericon/12322/123226612.jpg?1646346916</user_icon_url></thumb></nicovideo_thumb_response>
