<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<nicovideo_thumb_response status="ok"><thumb><video_id>sm45166271</video_id><title>ΔXIUS LIИK — RΞBØЯИ (2017) ジャンル: ダークエレクトロニック / ウィッチハウス Genre: Dark Electronic / Witch House</title><description>Our world is so far away, and yet I can reach out and touch you. You may know almost nothing about the music posted in the West. But I know almost nothing about the East. Because I care about each and every one of you, I wanted to bring NND music that touches your heart, music that you would probably not have imagined without the power of suggestion. To be clear, this music is not mine. But I have a heart that craves your happiness. And I'm so hungry. From us to you, enjoy delicious food!Our worlds are so distant, yet I could reach out and touch you. You have almost no idea about some of the music posted around the Western world, however, I have not much clue about the Eastern world. Because I cherish each and every one of you, I thought I'd bring music to NND that could appeal to some of you, music that you likely couldn't imagine on your own without the power of suggestion. To be clear, I do not own this music, however, I do own a heart that hungers for your happiness, and I'm quite hungry. Enjoy something delicious, from us to you!Source: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RPgmGtCQCzU</description><thumbnail_url>https://nicovideo.cdn.nimg.jp/thumbnails/45166271/45166271.55319191</thumbnail_url><first_retrieve>2025-07-08T14:06:05+09:00</first_retrieve><length>68:36</length><movie_type>mp4</movie_type><size_high>1</size_high><size_low>1</size_low><view_counter>4</view_counter><comment_num>0</comment_num><mylist_counter>0</mylist_counter><last_res_body/><watch_url>https://www.nicovideo.jp/watch/sm45166271</watch_url><thumb_type>video</thumb_type><embeddable>1</embeddable><no_live_play>0</no_live_play><tags domain="jp"/><genre>音楽・サウンド</genre><user_id>140588764</user_id><user_nickname>IamVM6</user_nickname><user_icon_url>https://secure-dcdn.cdn.nimg.jp/nicoaccount/usericon/14058/140588764.jpg?1750485847</user_icon_url></thumb></nicovideo_thumb_response>
