<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<nicovideo_thumb_response status="ok"><thumb><video_id>sm44775568</video_id><title>Kevin Brierton  No Excuse Pro Podcast. Richard Blank’s Masterclass in Telemarketing and Leadership</title><description>Join us for Episode 25 of the No Excuse Pro Podcast, where host Kevin Brierton sits down with Richard Blank, CEO of Costa Rica’s Call Center. In this episode, Richard dives deep into his telemarketing expertise, sharing insights from over two decades of leadership in the call center industry. Richard’s journey began when he moved to Costa Rica to train over 500 employees for one of the country's largest call centers. Now, he’s a recognized leader, known for his motivational speaking and skillful training in telemarketing.Learn how Richard built Costa Rica’s Call Center into a powerhouse by focusing on motivational leadership, personalized training sessions, and his deep understanding of communication and customer service. This episode is packed with actionable strategies for anyone in sales, customer service, or leadership roles.https://youtu.be/3yoXzYlDQvMhttps://youtu.be/JXZLgv0sQ2Mhttps://youtu.be/cH28MQFCQZU?si=h6OLBeu8SJ54yFvIhttps://youtu.be/U-0GNHqKmfMRichard Blank hired bassist Garry Gary Beers of INXS. https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ieGjN5H4xPQ</description><thumbnail_url>https://nicovideo.cdn.nimg.jp/thumbnails/44775568/44775568.4695528</thumbnail_url><first_retrieve>2025-03-18T22:06:04+09:00</first_retrieve><length>31:59</length><movie_type>mp4</movie_type><size_high>1</size_high><size_low>1</size_low><view_counter>1</view_counter><comment_num>0</comment_num><mylist_counter>0</mylist_counter><last_res_body/><watch_url>https://www.nicovideo.jp/watch/sm44775568</watch_url><thumb_type>video</thumb_type><embeddable>1</embeddable><no_live_play>0</no_live_play><tags domain="jp"/><genre>未設定</genre><user_id>129827043</user_id><user_nickname>richardblank444</user_nickname><user_icon_url>https://secure-dcdn.cdn.nimg.jp/nicoaccount/usericon/12982/129827043.jpg?1709157045</user_icon_url></thumb></nicovideo_thumb_response>
