<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<nicovideo_thumb_response status="ok"><thumb><video_id>sm44811982</video_id><title>Procrastinator's Pitstop. Host Chris Abdey and CEO Richard Blank discuss Procrastination to Purpose.</title><description>Procrastinator's Pitstop: Your Place to Refuel for Motivation and Productivity. Join us as we explore actionable strategies, inspiring stories, and expert insights to help you overcome procrastination and power through your to-do list. Let's turn every pitstop into progress!In this engaging conversation, Richard Blank, CEO of Costa Rica's Call Center, shares his insights on procrastination, personal growth, and the importance of communication. He discusses his journey from Northeast Philadelphia to Costa Rica, the challenges he faced in adapting to a new culture, and how he inspires his team to grow. Richard emphasizes the significance of creating a positive work environment and the art of effective communication, all while sharing his passion for restoring pinball machines.-Procrastination is a self-reflection of missed opportunities.-Commitment to oneself is key to overcoming procrastination.-Cultural adaptation requires patience and respect.-Staying healthy is essential for productivity.https://youtu.be/TEWjig764Oghttps://youtu.be/jmcE4y5QK1ghttps://youtu.be/83xKp-KatRo</description><thumbnail_url>https://nicovideo.cdn.nimg.jp/thumbnails/44811982/44811982.92023703</thumbnail_url><first_retrieve>2025-03-27T07:37:03+09:00</first_retrieve><length>42:07</length><movie_type>mp4</movie_type><size_high>1</size_high><size_low>1</size_low><view_counter>1</view_counter><comment_num>0</comment_num><mylist_counter>0</mylist_counter><last_res_body/><watch_url>https://www.nicovideo.jp/watch/sm44811982</watch_url><thumb_type>video</thumb_type><embeddable>1</embeddable><no_live_play>0</no_live_play><tags domain="jp"/><genre>未設定</genre><user_id>129827043</user_id><user_nickname>richardblank444</user_nickname><user_icon_url>https://secure-dcdn.cdn.nimg.jp/nicoaccount/usericon/12982/129827043.jpg?1709157045</user_icon_url></thumb></nicovideo_thumb_response>
