<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<nicovideo_thumb_response status="ok"><thumb><video_id>sm44805479</video_id><title>Pivoting to Web3 Podcast. AI and the future of call centres with Donna Mitchell and Richard Blank</title><description>Welcome to another exciting episode of the "Pivoting to Web3 Podcast." I'm your host, Donna Mitchell, and today, we have a very special guest who's a pioneer in the call center industry, Richard Blank. At just 27, Richard moved from Philadelphia to Costa Rica and eventually founded Costa Rica's Call Center in 2008, which has now grown to a 150-seat operation. Richard's focus on empathy in technology makes him a unique voice in the sector.In this episode, Richard will share his journey from studying Spanish at the University of Arizona to establishing a booming call center business in Central America. We'll delve into his thoughts on ethical campaigns, the importance of non-aggressive but assertive scripts, and the benefits of using offshore call centers for cost-effectiveness and scalability. Richard also talks about the integration of AI in call centers, stressing that while AI can increase efficiency, it cannot replace human empathy.https://youtu.be/dzK9R6v7ymshttps://youtu.be/gFUr6IMPUdwhttps://youtu.be/F31cDCU_-kIhttps://youtu.be/yV9DvkMkskw</description><thumbnail_url>https://nicovideo.cdn.nimg.jp/thumbnails/44805479/44805479.2742436</thumbnail_url><first_retrieve>2025-03-26T01:13:03+09:00</first_retrieve><length>34:40</length><movie_type>mp4</movie_type><size_high>1</size_high><size_low>1</size_low><view_counter>2</view_counter><comment_num>0</comment_num><mylist_counter>0</mylist_counter><last_res_body/><watch_url>https://www.nicovideo.jp/watch/sm44805479</watch_url><thumb_type>video</thumb_type><embeddable>1</embeddable><no_live_play>0</no_live_play><tags domain="jp"/><genre>未設定</genre><user_id>129827043</user_id><user_nickname>richardblank444</user_nickname><user_icon_url>https://secure-dcdn.cdn.nimg.jp/nicoaccount/usericon/12982/129827043.jpg?1709157045</user_icon_url></thumb></nicovideo_thumb_response>
