<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<nicovideo_thumb_response status="ok"><thumb><video_id>sm44797712</video_id><title>The First 15 Minutes of Star Wars: The Clone Wars (GameCube)</title><description>Copied from MobyGames:Beginning where Star Wars Episode II: Attack of the Clones left off, you must take control of either Anakin Skywalker, Mace Windu or Obi-Wan Kenobi and lead the Republic Army against the Confederacy of Independent Systems.After the Battle of Geonosis, Anakin and Obi Wan are sent to patrol a dead part of Republic sector, until a massive Confederate fleet ambushes the useless planet of Rhen Var. After this, Anakin, Obi Wan soon discover that there may be something darker. They find out about the Dark Reaper, an evil and powerful Sith device that could harvest the power of the living and use it as a concentrated weapon. Now it is up to the Republic to prevent this weapon from ever activating and destroying the galaxy!The Clone Wars has you deep inside the battles of the Old Republic through 16 missions, piloting a range of vehicles, as well as the weapon of the Jedi, your lightsaber. Whereas the Rogue Squadron series concentrated on aerial battles, The Clone Wars contains almost all ground battles.</description><thumbnail_url>https://nicovideo.cdn.nimg.jp/thumbnails/44797712/44797712.98822758</thumbnail_url><first_retrieve>2025-03-23T22:22:03+09:00</first_retrieve><length>15:00</length><movie_type>mp4</movie_type><size_high>1</size_high><size_low>1</size_low><view_counter>13</view_counter><comment_num>0</comment_num><mylist_counter>0</mylist_counter><last_res_body/><watch_url>https://www.nicovideo.jp/watch/sm44797712</watch_url><thumb_type>video</thumb_type><embeddable>1</embeddable><no_live_play>0</no_live_play><tags domain="jp"><tag lock="1">StarWars:TheCloneWars</tag><tag lock="1">クローン大戦</tag><tag lock="1">GameCube</tag><tag lock="1">NGC</tag><tag lock="1">ゲームキューブ</tag><tag lock="1">gameplay</tag></tags><genre>ゲーム</genre><user_id>123226612</user_id><user_nickname>The_VNS</user_nickname><user_icon_url>https://secure-dcdn.cdn.nimg.jp/nicoaccount/usericon/12322/123226612.jpg?1646346916</user_icon_url></thumb></nicovideo_thumb_response>
