<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<nicovideo_thumb_response status="ok"><thumb><video_id>sm45066704</video_id><title>The First 15 Minutes of Capcom Generation 第5集格闘家たし: Street Fighter II' Turbo (PlayStation)</title><description>Copied from MobyGames:Capcom Generation 第5集格闘家たし contains ports of the following titles, available for the first time on the PlayStation and SEGA Saturn:- Street Fighter II: The World Warrior- Street Fighter II': Champion Edition- Street Fighter II': Turbo - Hyper FightingCopied from Infogalactic:Street Fighter II' Turbo: Hyper Fighting is a competitive fighting game released for the arcades by Capcom in 1992. It is the third game in the Street Fighter II sub-series of Street Fighter games following Street Fighter II': Champion Edition. Released less than a year after the previous installment, Hyper Fighting introduced a faster playing speed and new special moves for certain characters, as well as further refinement to the character balance.Hyper Fighting is the final arcade game in the Street Fighter II series to use the CP System hardware. The next game in the series, Super Street Fighter II, switched to the CP System II hardware.</description><thumbnail_url>https://nicovideo.cdn.nimg.jp/thumbnails/45066704/45066704.38720884</thumbnail_url><first_retrieve>2025-06-08T15:18:05+09:00</first_retrieve><length>15:00</length><movie_type>mp4</movie_type><size_high>1</size_high><size_low>1</size_low><view_counter>0</view_counter><comment_num>0</comment_num><mylist_counter>0</mylist_counter><last_res_body/><watch_url>https://www.nicovideo.jp/watch/sm45066704</watch_url><thumb_type>video</thumb_type><embeddable>1</embeddable><no_live_play>0</no_live_play><tags domain="jp"><tag lock="1">PlayStation</tag><tag lock="1">PS1</tag><tag lock="1">プレイステーション</tag><tag lock="1">gameplay</tag><tag lock="1">ストリートファイターⅡダッシュターボ</tag><tag lock="1">Street_Fighter_II_Turbo</tag></tags><genre>ゲーム</genre><user_id>123226612</user_id><user_nickname>The_VNS</user_nickname><user_icon_url>https://secure-dcdn.cdn.nimg.jp/nicoaccount/usericon/12322/123226612.jpg?1646346916</user_icon_url></thumb></nicovideo_thumb_response>
