<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<nicovideo_thumb_response status="ok"><thumb><video_id>sm45055784</video_id><title>Brock the Rock Talks podcast guest Richard Blank Costa Ricas Call Center</title><description>Welcome to the “Brock The Rock Talks Podcast!” A podcast that talks about Entrepreneurship and the Real Deal of being a Dad, a Coach, a Speaker and a Realtor. This is me sharing my real life, the sh*# I go through, people in my life, the relentless lifestyle that I live, that flirts with obsession, the crazy thoughts in my head..Richard Blank, a Philadelphia native, moved to Costa Rica at 27 to follow his passion for Spanish and entrepreneurship. He combined his love for the language with the rich Costa Rican culture, creating a successful bilingual telemarketing business. Along the way, he learned the importance of soft skills, eliminating bad habits, and leading by example. Richard emphasizes staying disciplined, focused, and resilient in business, and how embracing adversity helped him build a strong foundation for his career and life. His story is a powerful reminder of the value of passion, perseverance, and leadership.Richard’s journey in the call center space is filled with twists and turns. When he was 27 years old, he relocated to Costa Rica to train employees for one of the larger call centers in San Jose. https://youtu.be/0dfmOORoxbQ</description><thumbnail_url>https://nicovideo.cdn.nimg.jp/thumbnails/45055784/45055784.31428675</thumbnail_url><first_retrieve>2025-06-05T07:05:03+09:00</first_retrieve><length>32:10</length><movie_type>mp4</movie_type><size_high>1</size_high><size_low>1</size_low><view_counter>4</view_counter><comment_num>0</comment_num><mylist_counter>0</mylist_counter><last_res_body/><watch_url>https://www.nicovideo.jp/watch/sm45055784</watch_url><thumb_type>video</thumb_type><embeddable>1</embeddable><no_live_play>0</no_live_play><tags domain="jp"/><genre>未設定</genre><user_id>140169727</user_id><user_nickname>RichardBlank44</user_nickname><user_icon_url>https://secure-dcdn.cdn.nimg.jp/nicoaccount/usericon/defaults/blank.jpg</user_icon_url></thumb></nicovideo_thumb_response>
