<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<nicovideo_thumb_response status="ok"><thumb><video_id>sm45278044</video_id><title>【TAS】GBA　遊☆戯☆王デュエルモンスターズ インターナショナル ワールドワイドエディション（北米版）</title><description>転載元https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WcvKmkJ5UaQ以下説明文This is a tool-assisted speedrun. For more information, see https://tasvideos.org/6674MTAS originally published on 2025-08-10Yu-Gi-Oh! Worldwide Edition: Stairway to the Destined Duel is a collectable card video game for the Game Boy Advance and a spin-off of the Yu-Gi-Oh! Duel Monsters anime and manga. It adapts the original collectible card game of the same name and the ruleset that was established at the time of the video game's release. Here, you challenge characters from the Duel Monsters anime to duels in various tournaments, whether it would be the KaibaCorp Cup where the winner faces Seto Kaiba or Limitation tournaments where there are extra rules on what cards are allowed. By winning matches, you can get more cards to add to your deck in addition to the five cards you get every week from the magazine Duelist Weekly.In this run, lapogne36 ( https://tasvideos.org/Users/Profile/lapogne36) goes for unlocking the Limitation tournaments as fast as possible and completing all ten of them in record time, manipulating the RNG and the AI the entire time.</description><thumbnail_url>https://nicovideo.cdn.nimg.jp/thumbnails/45278044/45278044.30522</thumbnail_url><first_retrieve>2025-08-11T10:31:03+09:00</first_retrieve><length>41:01</length><movie_type>mp4</movie_type><size_high>1</size_high><size_low>1</size_low><view_counter>294</view_counter><comment_num>32</comment_num><mylist_counter>1</mylist_counter><last_res_body>ｗｗｗｗｗｗｗｗｗ 就職したくらいで... 破壊輪つええええ ん？ バトルシティのク... 北米版なのに通行... ひでえｗ おい馬鹿やめろ！ ...</last_res_body><watch_url>https://www.nicovideo.jp/watch/sm45278044</watch_url><thumb_type>video</thumb_type><embeddable>1</embeddable><no_live_play>0</no_live_play><tags domain="jp"><tag lock="1">ゲーム</tag><tag lock="1">TAS</tag><tag lock="1">遊戯王</tag><tag lock="1">遊戯王マスターデュエル</tag><tag lock="1">GBA</tag><tag>既出：sm45160228</tag><tag>遊戯王TASリンク</tag><tag>カードは雑誌で拾った</tag></tags><genre>ゲーム</genre><user_id>5776708</user_id><user_nickname>グローリア</user_nickname><user_icon_url>https://secure-dcdn.cdn.nimg.jp/nicoaccount/usericon/577/5776708.jpg?1517923487</user_icon_url></thumb></nicovideo_thumb_response>
