<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<nicovideo_thumb_response status="ok"><thumb><video_id>sm44970356</video_id><title>Psalm [original song, Vocaloid, Lucas]</title><description>Although it sounds religious, it's not about religion. The phrasing may hint at this but the intent is more broad: of seeking solace in known, trusted sources, regardless of their efficacy.  OK, that does sound like religion ... but it's not what I had in mind.Tech NotesDrums sounds are Groove Agent with audio samples. Bass sounds from Retrologue, Subtractor &amp;amp; Malstrom (lots of processing), and Full Bucket Tricent emulator; orchestral samples from Reason for violin and clarinet; plus French Horn from Spitfire BBC. More synths from Halion, Arturia CS-80, Thor, Full Bucket Oxid. Vocal sounds from Bloom Vocal Aether and, finally, vocal synths are Vocaloid: Lucas, triple-tracked for added flavour.LyricsDo you sing for your wages?Psalm for the agesAll I want is your wordsClear among those fake sagesSmooth out your ragesPsalm for the agesAll I want is your wordsClear among those fake sagesPenny in the fountainSplashing hope around: ripples fadePutting trust in copper coinsSing for your wages?Psalm of the agesAll I want is your wordsClear among those fake sages</description><thumbnail_url>https://nicovideo.cdn.nimg.jp/thumbnails/44970356/44970356.77170598</thumbnail_url><first_retrieve>2025-05-10T22:56:03+09:00</first_retrieve><length>3:06</length><movie_type>mp4</movie_type><size_high>1</size_high><size_low>1</size_low><view_counter>32</view_counter><comment_num>0</comment_num><mylist_counter>0</mylist_counter><last_res_body/><watch_url>https://www.nicovideo.jp/watch/sm44970356</watch_url><thumb_type>video</thumb_type><embeddable>1</embeddable><no_live_play>0</no_live_play><tags domain="jp"><tag>VOCALOID</tag></tags><genre>音楽・サウンド</genre><user_id>132645476</user_id><user_nickname>richaux</user_nickname><user_icon_url>https://secure-dcdn.cdn.nimg.jp/nicoaccount/usericon/13264/132645476.jpg?1744128402</user_icon_url></thumb></nicovideo_thumb_response>
