<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<nicovideo_thumb_response status="ok"><thumb><video_id>sm44989315</video_id><title>Painting Portraits [Original Song, Vocaloid, Lucas &amp; Jessica]</title><description>The song built whilst doodling with sounds from the Full Bucket emulators -- e.g. https://www.fullbucket.de/music/paralogy.html -- lots of retro subtractive synthesis goodness. These framed the [spoiler alert] alarm sounds through the intro and the track spluttered into life (hopefully) from there. It paints a brief picture (ha, ha) of an artist trying to put their model at ease. There were more verses fluffing out the story but, thankfully, I didn't think the song needed them. Tech Notes Drums are from Reason Kong through assorted Reason hosted effects. Although the Reason instruments are all individually routable to Cubase -- as are the effects via VST -- sometimes it's just easier to stitch together at source. It is a fully fledged DAW in its own right. Guitary jangles are also from there using the Mimic sampler. There's a smorgasbord of synths from (deep breath) Full Bucket's emulators Bucket ONE (Bit 01) and Paralogy (Trilogy and Stratus), Reason Subtractor and Malstrom (piped through some Matrix Pattern shizzle), Halion Voltage, Arturia CS-80 , UAD PolyMAX, Retrologue, Olympus Choir. Vocal synths are courtesy of Vocaloid 6's Lucas &amp;amp; Jessica.</description><thumbnail_url>https://nicovideo.cdn.nimg.jp/thumbnails/44989315/44989315.53907757</thumbnail_url><first_retrieve>2025-05-16T19:29:03+09:00</first_retrieve><length>2:44</length><movie_type>mp4</movie_type><size_high>1</size_high><size_low>1</size_low><view_counter>18</view_counter><comment_num>0</comment_num><mylist_counter>0</mylist_counter><last_res_body/><watch_url>https://www.nicovideo.jp/watch/sm44989315</watch_url><thumb_type>video</thumb_type><embeddable>1</embeddable><no_live_play>0</no_live_play><tags domain="jp"><tag>VOCALOID</tag></tags><genre>音楽・サウンド</genre><user_id>132645476</user_id><user_nickname>richaux</user_nickname><user_icon_url>https://secure-dcdn.cdn.nimg.jp/nicoaccount/usericon/13264/132645476.jpg?1744128402</user_icon_url></thumb></nicovideo_thumb_response>
