<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<nicovideo_thumb_response status="ok"><thumb><video_id>sm45062277</video_id><title>Conversations Ignite Podcast presents Building Dreams in Costa Rica: pure Passion with Richard Blank</title><description>Welcome to "Conversations Ignite," where your host Robbie Ross brings you thought-provoking and entertaining interviews and stories. Dive into engaging discussions that explore diverse personalities and personal experiences, designed to ignite your curiosity and inspire your own journey.In this inspiring episode, we sit down with Richard Blank, the CEO of Costa Rica’s Call Center, who shares his remarkable journey from Philadelphia to Costa Rica at the age of 27. Richard talks about how his bilingual skills opened doors across Latin America and how he built his company from the ground up, overcoming numerous challenges along the way.We dive into his leadership philosophy, which focuses on empathy, motivation, and the power of human connection in the call center industry. Richard also discusses his unique approach to training over 10,000 bilingual telemarketers and the tools that have helped him succeed, like phonetic micro-expression reading and the famous Buffer-Boomerang Technique.https://youtu.be/MiiQN09fVbUhttps://youtu.be/O1c7pLF6gVs?si=yiLPtirltkpRG2aihttps://youtu.be/RVaF2wcKJ8chttps://youtu.be/-Q070aHSu6Ihttps://youtu.be/nhBjqu261HI</description><thumbnail_url>https://nicovideo.cdn.nimg.jp/thumbnails/45062277/45062277.74886756</thumbnail_url><first_retrieve>2025-06-07T02:44:03+09:00</first_retrieve><length>87:22</length><movie_type>mp4</movie_type><size_high>1</size_high><size_low>1</size_low><view_counter>3</view_counter><comment_num>0</comment_num><mylist_counter>0</mylist_counter><last_res_body/><watch_url>https://www.nicovideo.jp/watch/sm45062277</watch_url><thumb_type>video</thumb_type><embeddable>1</embeddable><no_live_play>0</no_live_play><tags domain="jp"/><genre>未設定</genre><user_id>140169727</user_id><user_nickname>RichardBlank44</user_nickname><user_icon_url>https://secure-dcdn.cdn.nimg.jp/nicoaccount/usericon/defaults/blank.jpg</user_icon_url></thumb></nicovideo_thumb_response>
