<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<nicovideo_thumb_response status="ok"><thumb><video_id>sm44791154</video_id><title>Hatsune Miku NT Whisper Vs. Hatsune Miku NT V2 Whisper 初音ミク (Miku and Mikune) Comparison</title><description>Hatsune Miku NT V2 Whisper has just been released, so I made a comparison video between Miku NT Whisper and Miku NT V2 Whisper without tuning or adding effects. Her voice is much better too, the sound quality the same and also the pitch, vibrato and the consonant length are tuning automatically according to the lyrics too. So, give them both a listen and decide for yourself! *Not just Miku NT V2 Whisper has been released. With Miku NT V2 Whisper being released, Miku NT V2 has been officially released!Lyrics and Video: Hatsune MikuneSinger: Hatsune MikuCredits: Miku and Mikune*Don't use our songs in any way. The illustrations either. These songs are made just for my Miku and in these illustrations is my Miku too. So, I don't want to be used by other people. Our songs are copyright protected. If someone uses our songs without permission, we will take appropriate measures. Thank you for your understanding and cooperation.You can find our songs on these sites too:YouTube https://www.youtube.com/@Miku-MikuneBioLink https://www.linktr.ee/Hatsune_Miku39© Miku and Mikune© All Rights Reserved</description><thumbnail_url>https://nicovideo.cdn.nimg.jp/thumbnails/44791154/44791154.17613707</thumbnail_url><first_retrieve>2025-03-21T18:32:04+09:00</first_retrieve><length>0:47</length><movie_type>mp4</movie_type><size_high>1</size_high><size_low>1</size_low><view_counter>29</view_counter><comment_num>0</comment_num><mylist_counter>1</mylist_counter><last_res_body/><watch_url>https://www.nicovideo.jp/watch/sm44791154</watch_url><thumb_type>video</thumb_type><embeddable>1</embeddable><no_live_play>0</no_live_play><tags domain="jp"><tag lock="1">初音ミク</tag><tag lock="1">VOCALOID</tag></tags><genre>音楽・サウンド</genre><user_id>128529782</user_id><user_nickname>Miku/Mikune</user_nickname><user_icon_url>https://secure-dcdn.cdn.nimg.jp/nicoaccount/usericon/12852/128529782.jpg?1715757686</user_icon_url></thumb></nicovideo_thumb_response>
