<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<nicovideo_thumb_response status="ok"><thumb><video_id>sm44991185</video_id><title>Hebrew Revival Blues１</title><description>(Verse 1) Oh, in the old land, where the desert winds moan, Hebrew was sleepin’, just a prayer carved in stone. Yeah, in the old land, where the shadows did roam, It was a dead tongue, no place to call home. (Verse 2) Came a man named Eliezer, with a fire in his soul, Said, “This language ain’t done, gonna make it whole.” Yeah, Ben-Yehuda, with his heart burnin’ bold, Wrote the words down, turned the dust into gold. (Chorus) Sing the Hebrew revival, oh, let it ring true, From the ashes of time, it’s a-comin’ for you. Through the struggle and pain, in the midnight’s deep hue, Hebrew’s alive, got the revival blues. (Verse 3) In ’48 we stood, with a nation newborn, Immigrants cryin’, their old lives torn. Yiddish and Russian, oh, the tongues they did roam, But Hebrew rose up, said, “This land is my home.” (Verse 4) They taught it in schools, in the fields and the streets, Kids learned the letters where the olive trees meet. From the synagogue’s chant to the market’s sweet beat, Hebrew was dancin’, oh, it moved their feet. (Chorus) Sing the Hebrew revival, oh, let it ring true, From the ashes of time, it’s a-comin’ for you. Through the struggle and pain, in the midnight’s deep hue,〜</description><thumbnail_url>https://nicovideo.cdn.nimg.jp/thumbnails/44991185/44991185.40217180</thumbnail_url><first_retrieve>2025-05-17T06:26:03+09:00</first_retrieve><length>3:48</length><movie_type>mp4</movie_type><size_high>1</size_high><size_low>1</size_low><view_counter>5</view_counter><comment_num>0</comment_num><mylist_counter>0</mylist_counter><last_res_body/><watch_url>https://www.nicovideo.jp/watch/sm44991185</watch_url><thumb_type>video</thumb_type><embeddable>1</embeddable><no_live_play>0</no_live_play><tags domain="jp"/><genre>音楽・サウンド</genre><user_id>88313948</user_id><user_nickname>びるばっとら</user_nickname><user_icon_url>https://secure-dcdn.cdn.nimg.jp/nicoaccount/usericon/8831/88313948.jpg?1564131645</user_icon_url></thumb></nicovideo_thumb_response>
