<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<nicovideo_thumb_response status="ok"><thumb><video_id>sm44985186</video_id><title>父家五</title><description>padreMan injures his mother and takes his own life in NaturaTIJUANA, BC - Monday, July 25, 2022 - AFN.9941Man injures his mother and takes his own life in Natura*.- He broadcast the events live on his Facebook account.Minutes after 10:00 p.m. this Monday in the city of Tijuana, a man took his own life. However, before doing so, he shot his mother, seriously wounding her. Neighbors alerted authorities, but they were unable to prevent what is believed to be a suicide.It was near the Natura neighborhood in the East Zone of the city where, inside a home, a man began shooting his approximately 70-year-old mother, alerting those living next door, who tried to intervene but were unable to enter.After shooting the woman, the man reportedly began streaming the incident live on his Facebook account and said goodbye to his loved ones. He then shot himself in the head, taking his own life.The reasons why the man began attacking his mother, as well as the motives that led him to take his own life and go public, are currently unknown. The woman was taken to a hospital by Mexican Red Cross paramedics.</description><thumbnail_url>https://nicovideo.cdn.nimg.jp/thumbnails/44985186/44985186.62629397</thumbnail_url><first_retrieve>2025-05-15T15:18:04+09:00</first_retrieve><length>2:09</length><movie_type>mp4</movie_type><size_high>1</size_high><size_low>1</size_low><view_counter>4</view_counter><comment_num>0</comment_num><mylist_counter>0</mylist_counter><last_res_body/><watch_url>https://www.nicovideo.jp/watch/sm44985186</watch_url><thumb_type>video</thumb_type><embeddable>1</embeddable><no_live_play>0</no_live_play><tags domain="jp"/><genre>未設定</genre><user_id>139666444</user_id><user_nickname>chapala.com</user_nickname><user_icon_url>https://secure-dcdn.cdn.nimg.jp/nicoaccount/usericon/13966/139666444.jpg?1745854348</user_icon_url></thumb></nicovideo_thumb_response>
