<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<nicovideo_thumb_response status="ok"><thumb><video_id>sm44887844</video_id><title>古神道修道士であり著述家の矢加部幸彦氏The author of Kannagara Ikishi is a Koshinto monk and author, *Yukihiko Yakabe</title><description>『神ながら意識』の著者は、古神道修道士であり著述家の**矢加部幸彦（やかべ ゆきひこ）**氏です。この書籍は2016年にナチュラルスピリット社から出版され、古神道の精神性や実践法、神道における宇宙観・神観について深く掘り下げています。また、古神道界の重鎮である大宮司朗氏からも推薦されています。 The author of Kannagara Ikishi is a Koshinto monk and author, **Yukihiko Yakabe**. The book was published by Natural Spirit in 2016 and delves deeply into Koshinto spirituality, practices, and the Shinto view of the universe and gods. It was also recommended by Omiya Shiro, a leading figure in the Koshinto world.*https://amzn.asia/d/903snzK矢加部氏は、神道のあり方、神社のこと、天皇家、鎮魂や禊（みそぎ）などのテーマをわかりやすく解説する活動を展開しており、古神道の教えや神社文化について広く啓蒙活動を行っています。Mr. Yagabe is engaged in activities that provide easy-to-understand explanations of themes such as the nature of Shinto, shrines, the Imperial family, and misogi (purification rituals), and is engaged in educational activities regarding the teachings of ancient Shinto and shrine cultureKoshinto is a primitive form of Shinto based on nature worship and ancestral faith that have been passed down since ancient times in Japan. It is also called "ancient Shinto" and refers to a simple faith rooted in daily life before the shrine system was established.</description><thumbnail_url>https://nicovideo.cdn.nimg.jp/thumbnails/44887844/44887844.23611736</thumbnail_url><first_retrieve>2025-04-18T07:31:03+09:00</first_retrieve><length>13:18</length><movie_type>mp4</movie_type><size_high>1</size_high><size_low>1</size_low><view_counter>20</view_counter><comment_num>0</comment_num><mylist_counter>0</mylist_counter><last_res_body/><watch_url>https://www.nicovideo.jp/watch/sm44887844</watch_url><thumb_type>video</thumb_type><embeddable>1</embeddable><no_live_play>0</no_live_play><tags domain="jp"/><genre>未設定</genre><user_id>120322024</user_id><user_nickname>EmilyJapan</user_nickname><user_icon_url>https://secure-dcdn.cdn.nimg.jp/nicoaccount/usericon/12032/120322024.jpg?1708724962</user_icon_url></thumb></nicovideo_thumb_response>
