<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<nicovideo_thumb_response status="ok"><thumb><video_id>sm45168217</video_id><title>No Messiah - メシアいない</title><description>A melodic house track in which Miku discusses the importance of the masses rising up themselves and not waiting for someone to save them. A lot of people are led to believe they are powerless and incapable of liberating and ruling themselves. In Wretched of the Earth, Fanon teaches us that these are colonial, bourgeois lies meant to stifle the masses’ revolutionary potential. In his words, “...we must above all rid ourselves of the very Western, very bourgeois and therefore contemptuous attitude that the masses are incapable of governing themselves. In fact, experience proves that the masses understand perfectly the most complicated problems” (187) and “To educate the masses ...is to try, relentlessly and passionately, to teach the masses that everything depends on them; that if we stagnate it is their responsibility, and that if we go forward it is due to them too, that there is no such thing as a demiurge, that there is no famous man who will take the responsibility for everything, but that the demiurge is the people themselves and the magic hands are finally only the hands of the people” (197).</description><thumbnail_url>https://nicovideo.cdn.nimg.jp/thumbnails/45168217/45168217.42729349</thumbnail_url><first_retrieve>2025-07-09T00:53:03+09:00</first_retrieve><length>3:40</length><movie_type>mp4</movie_type><size_high>1</size_high><size_low>1</size_low><view_counter>0</view_counter><comment_num>0</comment_num><mylist_counter>0</mylist_counter><last_res_body/><watch_url>https://www.nicovideo.jp/watch/sm45168217</watch_url><thumb_type>video</thumb_type><embeddable>1</embeddable><no_live_play>0</no_live_play><tags domain="jp"/><genre>音楽・サウンド</genre><user_id>140423223</user_id><user_nickname>Flam Chowder</user_nickname><user_icon_url>https://secure-dcdn.cdn.nimg.jp/nicoaccount/usericon/14042/140423223.jpg?1749355469</user_icon_url></thumb></nicovideo_thumb_response>
