<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<nicovideo_thumb_response status="ok"><thumb><video_id>sm44819005</video_id><title>Pacific West Home Builders</title><description>Deck Remodeling, Balcony Construction, Bedroom AdditionDreaming of a stunning outdoor retreat? Pacific West Home Builders specializes in deck remodeling that turns your backyard into an inviting living space. We design and build custom decks using premium materials to ensure durability, style, and seamless integration with your home's exterior.If your outdoor area is missing that perfect second-story getaway, our balcony construction services are just what you need. We offer contemporary, rustic, and classic styles designed for comfort, safety, and elegance. A new balcony not only enhances curb appeal but also adds usable square footage to your property.We’re also trusted leaders in bedroom addition services. Whether you need a nursery, office, or guest room, our team creates spaces that feel intentional and integrated. With our skilled architects and builders, we manage permits, structural plans, and construction, so your experience is stress-free.Pacific West Home Builders6320 Canoga Ave 15th Floor, Woodland Hills, CA 91367, United States888-398-4499http://pwhbuilders.com/</description><thumbnail_url>https://nicovideo.cdn.nimg.jp/thumbnails/44819005/44819005.65511114</thumbnail_url><first_retrieve>2025-03-29T06:48:03+09:00</first_retrieve><length>0:38</length><movie_type>mp4</movie_type><size_high>1</size_high><size_low>1</size_low><view_counter>4</view_counter><comment_num>0</comment_num><mylist_counter>0</mylist_counter><last_res_body/><watch_url>https://www.nicovideo.jp/watch/sm44819005</watch_url><thumb_type>video</thumb_type><embeddable>1</embeddable><no_live_play>0</no_live_play><tags domain="jp"/><genre>未設定</genre><user_id>139367569</user_id><user_nickname>pwhbuilders</user_nickname><user_icon_url>https://secure-dcdn.cdn.nimg.jp/nicoaccount/usericon/13936/139367569.jpg?1743198206</user_icon_url></thumb></nicovideo_thumb_response>
