<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<nicovideo_thumb_response status="ok"><thumb><video_id>sm45049761</video_id><title>AI Data Driven Leadership Podcast guest Richard Blank Costa Ricas Call Center</title><description>In this episode of AI &amp;amp; Data Driven Leadership, Dean Guida speaks to the President and Bilingual Telemarketer Trainer of Costa Rica's Call Center, Richard Blank. Richard emphasizes the irreplaceable value of human empathy and effective communication in customer interactions.He shares insights on hiring practices, training methods, and the importance of building client relationships. Richard also discusses balancing technology with the human touch, noting that while AI can streamline processes, genuine human connection remains essential. Richard highlights strategies for maintaining high-quality customer service and the significance of empathy in the digital age.https://youtu.be/suG9Kod45DIhttps://youtube.com/shorts/ZPIHkTowb7Yhttps://youtube.com/shorts/uT-kpgfBwWchttps://youtube.com/shorts/dHb1Y_I1s1IAI &amp;amp; Data Driven Leadership, Dean Guida, Richard Blank, Costa Rica's Call Center, Outsourcing, Telemarketing Call Centre, BPO, Nearshore Contact Center, Sales, Entrepreneur, B2B, Business, Podcast, Gamification,Leadership, Marketing, CX, Guest, Money, B2C education, BPO trainer,call centre, contact centre, contact center,trend, trending</description><thumbnail_url>https://nicovideo.cdn.nimg.jp/thumbnails/45049761/45049761.12228558</thumbnail_url><first_retrieve>2025-06-03T09:23:03+09:00</first_retrieve><length>49:20</length><movie_type>mp4</movie_type><size_high>1</size_high><size_low>1</size_low><view_counter>0</view_counter><comment_num>0</comment_num><mylist_counter>0</mylist_counter><last_res_body/><watch_url>https://www.nicovideo.jp/watch/sm45049761</watch_url><thumb_type>video</thumb_type><embeddable>1</embeddable><no_live_play>0</no_live_play><tags domain="jp"/><genre>未設定</genre><user_id>140169727</user_id><user_nickname>RichardBlank44</user_nickname><user_icon_url>https://secure-dcdn.cdn.nimg.jp/nicoaccount/usericon/defaults/blank.jpg</user_icon_url></thumb></nicovideo_thumb_response>
