<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<nicovideo_thumb_response status="ok"><thumb><video_id>sm45038298</video_id><title>AKB48+Me Ending + Credits + After game cutscene</title><description>Rights go to Nintendo and AKB48 (even if they split during 2020). the credits song: 少女たちよ by AKB48, had to be muted due to copyright This is footage of a game I've been playing recently because i thought itd be funny to put a male character in an japanese exclusive jpop girl game!There is not much knowledge of akb48+me online and i am willing to contribute as much footage and screenshots as i can to the internet. unfortunately, I do not speak or read japanese, so I cannot tell you what is specifically being said, but the game is so simple that i needed little to no translation. Abk48+me is a japanese exclusive game where your mii tries to get into the famous (at the time) jpop idol group, AKB48. It is a mix between rhythm game and management game. Your mii participates in performances, plays minigames on TV, and levels up their dancing, singing, and social skills to level up their popularity (again, this is all from what ive gathered playing the game with minimal knowledge of japanese). The game was played on my PC via Citra. the Citra site has a list of ROMs where you can search for the game and other games happy emulating! Keep games alive!</description><thumbnail_url>https://nicovideo.cdn.nimg.jp/thumbnails/45038298/45038298.30358735</thumbnail_url><first_retrieve>2025-05-31T02:29:03+09:00</first_retrieve><length>10:34</length><movie_type>mp4</movie_type><size_high>1</size_high><size_low>1</size_low><view_counter>5</view_counter><comment_num>0</comment_num><mylist_counter>0</mylist_counter><last_res_body/><watch_url>https://www.nicovideo.jp/watch/sm45038298</watch_url><thumb_type>video</thumb_type><embeddable>1</embeddable><no_live_play>0</no_live_play><tags domain="jp"/><genre>ゲーム</genre><user_id>140299629</user_id><user_nickname>monikamonimoni</user_nickname><user_icon_url>https://secure-dcdn.cdn.nimg.jp/nicoaccount/usericon/14029/140299629.jpg?1748624559</user_icon_url></thumb></nicovideo_thumb_response>
