<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<nicovideo_thumb_response status="ok"><thumb><video_id>sm45178138</video_id><title>Salty Ginger Talk Interview guest Richard Blank Costa Ricas Call Center</title><description>Welcome to Salty Ginger Talk, a podcast and video platform for people who want to improve themselves every single day. Hosted by Joe Canfield, this channel is built for thinkers, doers and self-leaders who are tired of excuses and ready to take control of their growth.We dive deep into powerful life principles like personal responsibility, emotional discipline, self-control and the stoic mindset. Whether it's solo reflections or raw conversations with bold entrepreneurs and purpose-driven leaders, each episode pushes you to think deeper and act better.What happens when you leave behind the noise, expectations, and pressure and chase your own vision?At just 27 years old, Richard Blank walked away from a life in Philadelphia to follow his intuition and built a 7-figure business in the heart of Costa Rica. In this episode of Salty Ginger Talk, we dive into Richard’s incredible transformation from dreamer to CEO of Costa Rica’s Call Centerhttps://youtu.be/fOJzuNTwvpQhttps://youtu.be/0rOyxBWRHCshttps://youtu.be/zas2ErvV-qkhttps://youtu.be/ilNdfNNHf4Ehttps://youtu.be/Pf4pDV__RQY</description><thumbnail_url>https://nicovideo.cdn.nimg.jp/thumbnails/45178138/45178138.78280606</thumbnail_url><first_retrieve>2025-07-12T05:54:03+09:00</first_retrieve><length>100:00</length><movie_type>mp4</movie_type><size_high>1</size_high><size_low>1</size_low><view_counter>0</view_counter><comment_num>0</comment_num><mylist_counter>0</mylist_counter><last_res_body/><watch_url>https://www.nicovideo.jp/watch/sm45178138</watch_url><thumb_type>video</thumb_type><embeddable>1</embeddable><no_live_play>0</no_live_play><tags domain="jp"/><genre>未設定</genre><user_id>140805938</user_id><user_nickname>richardblank</user_nickname><user_icon_url>https://secure-dcdn.cdn.nimg.jp/nicoaccount/usericon/defaults/blank.jpg</user_icon_url></thumb></nicovideo_thumb_response>
